

Guilherme Emilio Guain Peixinho Front-end Developer

- ⊠ guilherme.guain@gmail.com
- **(31)** 9 7609-8780

- © São Paulo, SP Brazil

I have been working with web development since 2012, when I started in a communication agency creating websites in Wordpress. After 8 years of experience in this technology, I started a specialization in React.js. In addition, I also follow Clean Code and SOLID principles, respecting technical SEO practices with a focus on problem solving.

HARD SKILLS HTML/CSS JAVASCRIPT/REACT.JS **TYPESCRIPT TECHNICAL SEO DESIGN/LAYOUT** GIT



TECHS & TOOLS

PRIMARY: React.js, TypeScript, Next.js, ESLint, Git, Tailwind CSS and Postman.

SECONDARY: PHP, Node.js, MySQL, WordPress, AMP,

GraphQL, Sass and Gulp.

DESIGN: Figma, Photoshop e Illustrator.

LANGUAGES

PORTUGUESE: Native ENGLISH: Intermediate

Experience

Amo Promo

FRONT-END DEVELOPER 01/2023 - present









With the purpose of promoting unforgettable experiences, I work in the planning and development of web and mobile solutions using the most modern technologies.

Toxicologia Pardini

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER 08/2018 - present















Reference company in toxicology testing where I act as a full-stack developer responsible for the development and maintenance of the site. Among the main activities are: on-page SEO optimization, implementation of new features, bug fixes and integrations with internal systems, CRM and ERP.

Inter-American Coalition

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER 08/2021 - present









Project developed with WordPress Multisite to unify the organization's websites, facilitating the maintenance and management of content. I am currently responsible for monitoring and maintaining the server, updating WordPress plugins and themes, and managing website content.

Education

UDACITY

Ignite Lab - Node.js, NestJS, Prisma and Jest ROCKETSEAT		HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and Bootstrap ALURA	11/2017 - 02/2018 Online
React.js - Ignite ROCKETSEAT		Programming logic and PHP	10/2012 - 06/2014 São Paulo, SP
GoStack - Node.js, React.js and React Native ROCKETSEAT	·	Graphic Design Technician ALPHA CHANNEL	05/2012 - 05/2013 São Paulo, SP
Nanodegree Front-end Web Developer	11/2017 - 04/2018		